双峰
第三季第十八集[本季终]
电
Electricity.
我在哪
Where am I?
稍等
Just a second.
道吉
Dougie!
爸爸
Dad?
爸爸  爸爸
Dad? Dad!
家
Home.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛  Silence  TheWalkingNerd  詹木头
翻译     Lynn_宁  Pang  吃冰棒  小酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     今  Jessie
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
这是
未来
还是
这是
过去
我
是
手臂
我
听起来像
这样
这
是
那个故事吗
关于那个
小
姑娘
她曾经住在
路口
是吗
找到
劳拉
是你吗
Is it you?
真的是你吗
Is it really you?
是的
Yes.
真的是我  戴安
It's really me, Diane.
真的是你吗
Is it really you?
是的
Yes.
你确定你想这么做吗
You sure you want to do this?
你不知道会变成什么样  一旦我们...
You don't know what it's gonna be like once we--
这我知道
I know that.
我们现在就在那个地方
We're at that point now.
我能感觉得到
I can feel it.
听着
Look.
差不多整整692公里
Almost exactly 430 miles.
整整692公里
Exactly 430 miles.
想清楚  库柏
Just think about it, Cooper.
就是这没错
This is the place, all right.
吻我
Kiss me.
我们一旦穿越  一切可能会改变
Once we cross, it could all be different.
走吧
Let's go.
汽车旅馆
把灯关掉
Turn off the light.
我们现在怎么办
What do we do now?
你走向我这儿
You come over here to me.
戴安
Diane.
Diane?
戴安
"亲爱的理查德..."
"Dear Richard..."
理查德
Richard?
"你看到这封信的时候  我已经离开了
"When you read this, I'll be gone.
请不要来找我
Please don't try to find me.
我已经不再认得你了
I don't recognize you anymore.
我们之间的一切都已经结束了
Whatever it was we had together is over.
琳达"
Linda."
理查德
Richard.
琳达
Linda.
敖德萨城区边界
人口数  99940
朱迪家餐厅
内有早餐  午餐  晚餐
要咖啡吗
Coffee?
-再来点咖啡  -好的
- More coffee? - Yes.
来点咖啡吗
Coffee?
这里还有别的服务生吗
Is there another waitress that works here?
有
Yeah.
她今天休息
It's her day off.
实际上  她已经休息三天了
Actually, it's her third day off.
再来点咖啡
More coffee?
住手
Stop it.
Stop it!
住手  住手
Stop. Stop!
放开她
Leave her alone.
你他妈在干什么
What the fuck you doing?
什么
What?
滚出去
Get the fuck out of that booth.
操
Oh, fuck!
靠
Oh, shit!
操
Oh, shit.
把你的枪放在地上
Put your gun on the ground.
我没有枪
I don't have a gun.
把你的枪放在地上
Put your gun on the ground.
坐下
Sit down.
该死
Oh, shit.
混蛋
Motherfucker.
该死
Shit.
操
Fuck.
该死
Shit.
他是谁
Who is he?
把地址写在一张纸上
Write the address on a piece of paper.
什么
What?
把另一个服务生的地址
Write the address of the other waitress
写在一张纸上
on a piece of paper.
这要放在哪里
Where does this go?
什么
What?
这个要放在哪里
Where do you hang this?
上面的槽里
Above, in the slot.
我不知道这些油会不会烫到融化这些子弹
I don't know if the oil's hot enough to set off those bullets,
但如果是我就会让开
but I'd move away.
你把她的地址给我写下来了吗
Did you write down her address for me?
嗯  但是...
Yeah, but, um...
没事的
It's okay.
我是联调局的
I'm with the FBI.
联调局
FBI?
刚刚发生了什么
What the fuck just happened? -
他是谁
Who is it?
联邦调查局
FBI.
你找到他了吗
Did you find him?
劳拉
Laura.
你没找到他吗
You didn't find him?
劳拉
Laura.
你找错人了  先生
You got the wrong house, mister.
你是说你不是劳拉·帕尔默吗
You're saying you're not Laura Palmer?
劳拉什么
Laura who?
不  我不是她
No, I'm not her.
现在
Now--
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
嘉莉·佩吉
Carrie Page.
Carrie Page?
是的
That's right.
现在我要关门了  所以
Now, I got to go, so...
等等
Wait.
所以你对劳拉·帕尔默一点印象都没有吗
So the name Laura Palmer means nothing to you?
听着
Look...
我不知道你想要什么
I don't know what you want,
但是我不是她
but I'm not her.
你父亲叫利兰
Your father's name was Leland.
好吧
Okay.
你妈妈叫萨拉
Your mother's name is Sarah.
萨拉
S-Sarah?
是的  萨拉
Yes, Sarah.
怎么了
What's going on?
很难解释
It's difficult to explain.
和听起来一样奇怪
As strange as it sounds,
我觉得你叫劳拉·帕尔默
I think you're a girl named Laura Palmer.
我想带你回你母亲家...
I want to take you to your mother's home...
也就是你家
your home at one time.
这很重要
It's very important.
听着...
Listen...
通常来说...
normally...
你这样的人上门来
somebody like you comes around,
我会让他滚蛋
and I tell him to fuck off.
我会直接把门摔在他们的脸上
This door would be slammed in their face.
现在
Right now
反正我也要离开道奇
I got to get out of Dodge anyway.
说来话长
It's a long story.
所以坐联调局的车可能可以救我一命
So riding with the FBI just might save my ass.
我们去哪
Where we going?
华盛顿双峰镇
Twin Peaks, Washington.
华盛顿市吗
D.C.?
不  华盛顿州
No, state.
华盛顿州
Washington State.
很远吗
It's a long way?
很远很远
It's a ways away.
我去拿东西  请进
Let me get my things. Come on in.
等我一下
Give me a minute.
华盛顿
Washington.
是不是在北边
Is that, like, up north?
需要带外套吗
Do I need a coat?
有外套就带上吧
Take a coat if you've got one.
我有好几件
I've got a couple.
我去拿一件
I'll grab one.
听着...
Listen...
我这没有吃的
I don't have any food here.
我在路上买点吃的
I'll get us some food on the way.
好吧
All right.
走吧
Let's go.
你真的是联调局特工吗
Are you really an FBI agent?
是的
Yes.
至少我们离开了这个该死的敖德萨小镇
Well, at least we're getting out of this fucking town of Odessa.
有人跟着我们吗
Is someone following us?
敖德萨
Odessa.
我试着保持屋内整洁...
I tried to keep a clean house...
让所有东西都尽然有序
...keep everything organized.
一切都很漫长
It's a long way.
那些时候
In those days...
我太年轻了  不知道还有别的
...I was too young to know any better.
你记起什么了吗
You recognize anything?
没有
No.
你认得那幢房子吗
You recognize that house?
不
No.
来吧
Come on.
哪位
Yes?
联调局的
FBI
我是戴尔·库柏特工
I'm Special Agent Dale Cooper.
萨拉·帕尔默住在这里吗
Is Sarah Palmer here?
谁
Who?
萨拉·帕尔默
Sarah Palmer.
不  没有这个人
No, there's no one here by that name.
你认识萨拉·帕尔默吗
Do you know Sarah Palmer?
不认识
No.
这是你的家吗
Is this your house?
这房子是你的吗
Do you own this house,
还是说是你租的
or do you rent this house?
这房子是我们的
Yes, we own this house.
你向谁买的
Who did you buy it from?
亲爱的  卖房子给我们的那个女人叫什么
Honey, what was the name of the woman who sold us the house?
切尔方特  切尔方特太太
Chalfont, a Mrs. Chalfont.
那你知道她是向谁买的这幢房子吗
Do you happen to know who she bought it from?
不  我不知道  但是
No, I don't, but...
亲爱的  你知道这房子在切尔方特太太前是谁的吗
Honey, do you know who owned it before Mrs. Chalfont?
不知道
No.
你叫什么
What is your name?
爱丽丝  爱丽丝·特里蒙特
Alice. Alice Tremond.
好吧
Okay.
抱歉这么晚来打扰你
Sorry to bother you so late at night.
没事
That's okay.
晚安
Good night.
今年是几几年
What year is this?
劳拉
Laura!